<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Jacy Wang]]></title>
  <link href="http://jacywang.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://jacywang.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-11-23T17:34:20-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://jacywang.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Jacy Wang]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start My New Journey]]></title>
    <link href="http://jacywang.github.io/blog/2014/11/23/start-my-new-journey/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-23T16:25:29-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://jacywang.github.io/blog/2014/11/23/start-my-new-journey</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today is Nov 23rd, 2014 and I just finished Lesson 3 on TeaLeaf Academy.</p>

<p>It has been three weeks since I joined the program and I was surprised by the progress I made. In three weeks, I built up three games in two different approach, procedural and OO. Then game Blackjack was upgraded from the command line to the web by using Sinatra. And today I have my own blog based on <a href="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</a>. This is awesome!</p>

<p>Before joining the program, I have been going through different tutorials online but in the end, I&rsquo;m still wondering where I should start and lacking confidence in building up web applications. After doing a lot of research and visiting bootcamps in Toronto, I chose TeaLeaf because it&rsquo;s online, cheaper and I don&rsquo;t need to quit my full time job. Its alumni also gave very positive feedback.</p>

<p>Why am I doing this? To make more money. Yes, that&rsquo;s why I started. But as I get more and more knowledge and practice, it becomes more and more interesting for me. I love it! Two hours a day from Monday to Friday and over 10 hours in the weekend were spent on it. I&rsquo;m addicted to it, like chocolate.</p>

<p>I know it&rsquo;s a long process and requires patience and commitment to become really good at it. But it&rsquo;s never too late to start. I would like to record this experience and write down the tips I learnt and mistakes I made.</p>

<p><code>Hello world!</code></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
